

Viet Tran Full-Stack Web Developer



+358 45 105 3344



vietth@msn.com



Savikuja 2i 31, 02770, Espoo



https://viet.netlify.app

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am currently a fourth year student at the Metropolia University of Applied Sciences. Although my major is Mobile Solution, I have a passion for the web-devenopment.

I have over 10 years of experience working in the information technology environment in Vietnam.

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS/JSS/SASS,
- Javascript (ES6)
- React: Redux, React Hooks (Custom Hooks, Context API,...)
- UI Frameworks: Material UI, Semantic
- Apollo Client, Apollo Server
- Nodejs: Rest API, Graphql
- Database: MongoDB, MariaDB

EDUCATION

1997 - 2002 Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Major: Electronics and Telecommunication

Graduated: Electronics and Telecommunications Engineer

2004 - 2006 Military Technology Academy

Major: Information Technology Graduated: Master of Technology

2017 - current Metropolia University of Applied Sciences

Major: Mobile Solution

EXPERIENCE

2002 - 2004 Haiphong Software Park (HSP) Viet Nam

Web Developer

HTML/CSS, Javascript, ASP.NET, SQLDB

2004 - 2011 Vietnam Maritime Communications and Electronic LLC (Vishipel)

Project Manager

Constructing and implementing a number of major projects of Vietnam's maritime industry:

- Ship Registration Management
- Crew Management
- Human Resource Management
- Document Management

2010 The merit of the Ministry of Transport Vietnam

"There have been many achievements in research and applied of science and technology for transportation from 2005 to 2010"